>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 有角落的例子，我们知道这就是现实，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So there are corner
cases, we know that that's the reality,
有角落的案子
there were corner cases.
我们不处理任何语言的角落案件 JavaScript
We don't deal with corner cases in any
language but least of all, JavaScript,
就能避免这种情况
by simply avoiding it.
你不回避整个机制只需要解决几个角落的问题。
You don't avoid the whole mechanism just
to get around a couple of corner cases.
>> Kyle Simpson: 您必须采用一种编码样式，使您的类型和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You have to adopt
a coding style that makes your types and
这些类型的值显而易见
the values that are in those
types plain and obvious,
这才是唯一有效的方法
that's the only effective way to do this.
有些人到目前为止还用了完整的系统
Some people goes so
far as to used whole type systems, and
我们就会变得有点像 TypeScript 之类的东西
we'll get into that a little bit
later like TypeScript and stuff.
我不认为你要走那么远但你可以采用一种编码方式
I don't think you have to go that far but
you can adopt a coding style which makes
你所做的各种类型都是显而易见的
the kinds of types that you're
doing much more obvious.
我声称一个质量好的 JavaScript 程序
I make the claim that a quality
JavaScript program is going to have to
拥抱胁迫
embrace coercion.
您必须确保每个操作所涉及的类型都是明确的。
You have to make sure that the types
involved in every operation are clear.
这意味着你不应该设计这些
And by the way that means that you
shouldn't be designing all these
可采取任何形式值的多态函数
polymorphic functions that can
take any sort of value and
根据价值做 15 种不同的事情
do 15 different things
based upon the value.
当你这么做的时候你要求的是胁迫问题
You're asking for
coercion problems when you do that and
但我用了三级分我用了三等同物
then papering over them, but I used
the triple, I used the triple equals.
为什么不只是设计一个只需要数字和
Why not just design a function
that only takes numbers and
然后再做一个只需要字符串的函数吗
then make another function
that only takes strings?
或者创建一个函数，该函数采用数字和字符串，并且
Or make a function that takes numbers and
strings, and
很明显只能是这两类
it's very clear it can only
be those two types, and
我知道我需要担心的是数字和字符串之间的关系。
I know what corner cases I have to worry
about between numbers and strings.
我们可以选择更清楚地了解我们如何管理我们的类型，
We can choose to be more obvious
about how we manage our types,
我们过载多少多态有多多态
how much we overload,
how polymorphic we make our code.
因此，我们可以选择更多问题，或选择不存在问题。
We can opt in to more problems or
opt out of problems as a result.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我想让你来的最大的外卖就是这些
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Biggest takeaway that
I want you to get here is that these
是您计划的事实，并在您的权限范围内决定
are fact of your programs and it is
within your purview to decide how much or
你会受到这些事实的影响
how little you're gonna be
affected by those facts.
>> Kyle Simpson: 这并不意味着我们问题的唯一解决方案是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That is not to suggest
that the only solution to our problem is
一切都必须严格地说一切都是静态的
that everything have to rigidly,
everything's completely statically typed.
我们要基本去写 Java 或者 C Plus Plus 好了
We have to just basically go write Java or
C Plus Plus so that we get some
就像声音系统一样，是对这个问题的一个反应，
kind of like sound type system,
that is a reaction to this problem,
这并不是我认为必要的反应。
it is not the the reaction
I think that is necessary.
所以我在这里宣扬的信息是你可以学习这些系统
So the message I'm preaching here
is you can learn these systems,
适当地使用它们并使它们在代码中很明显。
use them appropriately and
make them obvious in your code.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我不认为这个打字系统是薄弱环节，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I do not think that
this typing systems are weaknesses,
我认为这是 JavaScript 最强大的特质之一。
I actually think this is one of
JavaScript's strongest qualities.
这是一个无名英雄我认为这是 JavaScript 的原因之一
It's an unsung hero, I think it's
one of the reasons why JavaScript is
这种无所不在的语言是因为它一直如此
the ubiquitous language that it
is today because it has been so
对很多不同的用例都有问题
palatable to so many different use cases.
第一种真正的多范式语言和一个重要的原因
The first truly multi-paradigm
language and a big reason why it has
能够生存多重模式是因为它的类型系统。
been able to survive multi-paradigm
is because of its type system.
这与我的每一个同龄人和
And that's completely opposite from
what every one of my peers and
所有你听过的其他东西
everything else that you've ever heard.
每个人都告诉你这是 JavaScript 最糟糕的部分
Everybody else has always told you this
is the worst part of JavaScript and
我要把脚放下说这是最棒的部分
I'm gonna put my foot down and say it's
one of the best parts of JavaScript.
如果你没在用它你的程序就没了
And if you're not using it,
your programs are missing out